export const ar_trivia = [
    {
        question: 'This popular all-female krewe was named after the legendary daughters of Zeus. ',
        answer: 'Muses',
        options: [
            'Muses',
            'Sirion',
            'Hercules',
            'Medoza'
        ]
    }, {
        question: 'This dancing group, founded in 2018, wear suits inspired by mythology or traditions that deal with death, mortality or the afterlife.',
        answer: 'Dead Beans',
        options: [
            'Dead Beans',
            'Ninja Wolfs',
            'Ninja Stars',
            'Dead Lions'
        ]
    }, {
        question: 'This parade was the first to have flambeaux in 1857.',
        answer: 'Comus',
        options: [
            'Comus',
            'Colombus',
            'Moon',
            'Sharks'
        ]
    }, {
        question: 'In 1875, Governor Warmoth signed this act, making Fat Tuesday a legal holiday in Louisiana.',
        answer: 'The Mardi Gras Act',
        options: [
            'The Mardi Gras Act',
            'The Mardi Gras Carnival',
            'Mardi Gras Holiday',
            'Fat Cow day'
        ]
    }, {
        question: 'This rank of Mardi Gras Indian carries the gang flag.',
        answer: 'Flag Boy',
        options: [
            'Flag Boy',
            'Flag Man',
            'Flags',
            'Big Flag'
        ]
    }, {
        question: 'Rex’s official song “If Ever I Cease to Love” came from a 1870’s musical. Name it.',
        answer: 'Bluebeard',
        options: [
            'Bluebeard',
            'Redbeard',
            'Blackbeard',
            'Bigbeard'
        ]
    }, {
        question: 'This krewe’s motto is “Throw till it hurts.”',
        answer: 'Endymion',
        options: [
            'Endymion',
            'Anonimus',
            'K.K.K',
            'The Heartless'
        ]
    }, {
        question: 'This parade was the first to roll after Hurricane Katrina in 2006.',
        answer: 'Krewe du Vieux',
        options: [
            'Krewe du Vieux',
            'Never Give up',
            'Never Say Never',
            'Never Again'
        ]
    }, {
        question: 'Unicorns are not allowed in this parade (unless they have rocket thrusters). ',
        answer: 'The Intergalactic Krewe of Chewbacchus',
        options: [
            'The Intergalactic Krewe of Chewbacchus',
            'Krewe du Vieux',
            'Endymion',
            'Flag Boy Team Forever'
        ]
    }, {
        question: 'They choose their king and queen by whoever gets the babies in two king cakes.',
        answer: 'Phunny Phorty Fellows',
        options: [
            'Phunny Phorty Fellows',
            'The Intergalactic Krewe of Chewbacchus',
            'Krewe du Vieux',
            'Flag Boy Team Forever'
        ]
    }
];